<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">করোনা ইনফো</string>
    <string name="app_info_text_1" tools:ignore="Typos">আসসালমুয়ালাইকুম। আমার নাম মো: জোবায়ের। আমি ব্র্যাক বিশ্ববিদ্যালয়ের তড়িৎ প্রকৌশল বিভাগে অধ্যয়নরত। বর্তমান সময় পুরো মানব জাতির জন্য একটি সংকটপূর্ণ মুহূর্ত। সবার উচিত যার যার নিজের অবস্থান থেকে সাহায্যের হাত বাড়িয়ে দেওয়া। আর তাই আমিও আমার পক্ষ থেকে এই ছোট একটি উদ্যোগ নিলাম। এই অ্যাপ এর মাধ্যমে আপনি বর্তমান বাংলাদেশের করোনা পরিস্থিতি সম্পর্কে বেশ কিছু তথ্য পাবেন। এটি একটি অলাভজনক অ্যাপ। অর্থাৎ এর মাধ্যমে এর উদ্ভাবকগণ কোনো ভাবেই লাভবান হচ্ছেন না। এটি একটি সামাজিক উন্নয়নমূলক কাজ। আপনার কোনো ব্যক্তিগত তথ্য এই অ্যাপ এর দ্বারা অন্য কোথাও পাচার হচ্ছে না শুধুমাত্র এটা ব্যতিত যে এর উদ্ভাবকগণ Firebase Analytics ব্যবহার করে অ্যাপ এর আচরণবিধি পর্যবেক্ষণ করছেন, আপনি অ্যাপ এর কোন ফিচারটি বেশি ব্যবহার করছেন ইত্যাদি কিছু সাধারণ তথ্য ছাড়া।</string>
    <string name="app_info_text_2">অ্যাপটি বর্তমানে বাংলাদেশের করোনা পরিস্থিতি সম্পর্কে জানান দেওয়ার জন্য https://corona.in.com.bd এর API ব্যবহার করছে এবং তাদের তথ্যগুলো প্রদর্শন করছে। করোনা ইনফো এর উদ্ভাবকগণ তাদের নিকট চির কৃতজ্ঞ। তারা যে সামাজিক উন্নয়নমূলক কাজটি করছেন তা নিঃসন্দেহে প্রশংসনীয়। আমি তাদের সার্বিক উন্নতি কামনা করছি।</string>
    <string name="app_info_text_3">করোনা ইনফো অ্যাপটি সম্পূর্ণভাবে উন্মুক্ত। অ্যাপটি MIT License দ্বারা নিবন্ধিত। এটি আপনি আপনার প্রয়োজনমতো পরিবর্তন করে আপনার কাজে ব্যাবহার করতে পারেন। তবে এক্ষেত্রে আপনাকে অবশ্যই করোনা ইনফো অ্যাপ এর প্রকৃত উদ্ভাবকদের অবদান স্বীকার এবং উল্লেখ করতে হবে।</string>
    <string name="app_info_text_4">অ্যাপটি Shrikanth Ravi (https://github.com/shrikanth7698)\'র INDIA-COVID-19-Tracker অ্যাপ এর ডিজাইন দ্বারা অনুপ্রাণিত।</string>

    <string name="osl_pref">
        Copyright 2005-2011 The Android Open Source Project\n\n

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\n

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="osl_retrofit">
        Copyright 2013 Square, Inc.\n\n

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\n

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="osl_paper">
        Copyright 2015 Aleksey Masny\n\n

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\n

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="osl_firebase">
        License January 2004\n\n

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\n

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="osl_github_icon">
        Copyright 2020 Ionicons\n\n

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:\n\n

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n\n

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="osl_app_icon">
        Icon made by Freepik from flaticon.com
    </string>

</resources>
